https://www.acrolabels.com/privacy-policy/

(800)355-2235
2530 Wyandotte Rd, Willow Grove, PA 19090
Acro Labels Inc. Features Custom Label Services For All Major Industries
Home / Privacy Policy
Your privacy is critically important to us.
Acro Labels is located at:
Acro Labels
2530 Wyandotte Rd.
800.355.2235
It is Acro Labels’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. This Privacy Policy applies to https://www.acrolabels.com (hereinafter, “us”, “we”, or “https://www.acrolabels.com”). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through the Website. We have adopted this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) to explain what information may be collected on our Website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through the Website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.
This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms and conditions posted on our Website, set forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our Website. Depending on your activities when visiting our Website, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, Acro Labels collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Acro Labels’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Acro Labels’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Acro Labels may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
Acro Labels also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on https://www.acrolabels.com blog posts. Acro Labels only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to Acro Labels’s websites choose to interact with Acro Labels in ways that require Acro Labels to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Acro Labels gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a blog at https://www.acrolabels.com to provide a username and email address.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Advertisements
Ads appearing on our website may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Acro Labels and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Links To External Sites
Our Service may contain links to external sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy and terms and conditions of every site you visit.
We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites, products or services.
Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information
Acro Labels discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Acro Labels’s behalf or to provide services available at Acro Labels’s website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Acro Labels’s website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Acro Labels will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Acro Labels discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Acro Labels believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Acro Labels, third parties or the public at large.
If you are a registered user of https://www.acrolabels.com and have supplied your email address, Acro Labels may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Acro Labels and our products. We primarily use our blog to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Acro Labels takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.
Aggregated Statistics
Acro Labels may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. Acro Labels may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Acro Labels does not disclose your personally-identifying information.
Cookies
To enrich and perfect your online experience, Acro Labels uses “Cookies”, similar technologies and services provided by others to display personalized content, appropriate advertising and store your preferences on your computer.
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Acro Labels uses cookies to help Acro Labels identify and track visitors, their usage of https://www.acrolabels.com, and their website access preferences. Acro Labels visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Acro Labels’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Acro Labels’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
By continuing to navigate our website without changing your cookie settings, you hereby acknowledge and agree to Acro Labels’s use of cookies.
E-commerce
Those who engage in transactions with Acro Labels – by purchasing Acro Labels’s services or products, are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Acro Labels collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Acro Labels. Acro Labels does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Acro Labels may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Acro Labels’s sole discretion. Acro Labels encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
Contact Information
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us via sales@acrolabels.com or 800-355-2235.
Name:
Email:
Phone Number:
Comments:
Order ID:
Shape:
Width:
Length:
Material:
Coating:
Versions:
Quantity:
Ink:
Wind:
Finishing:
Total Job Cost:
Shipping Weight:
Date and Time:
Add to Cart
